Guide to the Papers of Lourdes Portillo, 1979¯2001 M1480
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 1979¯2001
  - Columbus on Trial, 1992
    - Columbus on Trial ¯ Viewing Copy, Video; VHS; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 43, Videotape 23)
    - Columbus ¯ SR 01¯17, 7/1992; 17.0 Items; Audio: 1/4"' open¯reel tape; Master; (Carton 54, Reel 1¯17)
    - Columbus ¯ DAT Pro Final Audio Mix Stereo, 10/1992; 2.0 Computer Media; Audio: Digital Audiotape; Master; 46 min (Carton 54, Audiocassettes 18¯19)
    - Columbus On Trial ¯ Background Material ¯ Tapes #1 & #2, 10/1992; 2.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub (Carton 54, Audiocassettes 20¯21)
  - El Diablo Nunca Duerme, 1994
    - Tio Oscar MOS Rolls (1¯10 of 16), 10.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 8, Reels 1¯10 of 16)
    - Tio Oscar MOS Rolls (11¯16 of 16), 6.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 9, Reels 11¯16 of 16)
    - Spanish Translation of Soundtrack: Sound Pre¯Mix Units #1¯#4, 12/1994; 4.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master; ~1000ft. each (Carton 10, Reels 1¯4)
    - Spanish Version of Soundtrack Mixed Unit #1¯#4, 4.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 10, Reels 5¯8)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Assembly Rolls #11¯13, #15¯16, nd; 5.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 11, Reels 1,3,5,7,9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Assembly Rolls #11¯13, #15¯16, nd; 5.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 11, Reels 2,4,6,8,10)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Fine Cut Pix Reels #1 & #2, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 13, Reels 1, 2)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Rough Cut Pix Reel #3 & #4, 12/1994; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 13, Reels 3, 4)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Reel #2 Dials 1¯4 Mag Out, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 13, Reels 5¯8)
    - [Five 35mm Film cans with 29 miscellaneous reels of 16mm and 35mm Film distributed within], 29.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Trims (Carton 14, Reels 1¯5)
    - [35mm Film Can with 2 large misc 16mm reels], nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Trims (Carton 15, Reel 1)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps 16mm Mono from 35mm Final Mix Reels 1¯4, 8/1994; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Trims (Carton 15, Reel 2¯5)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Assembly Roll #4¯6, 9¯10, nd; 5.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 16, Reels 1,3,5,7,9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Assembly Roll #4¯6, 9¯10, nd; 5.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 16, Reels 2,4,6,8,10)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps 3/4" Window Dub Reels 1¯4 (2 sets), 7/1994; 5.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic; Dub (Carton 17, Videotapes 1¯5)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps" Reels 2 & 4 from 3/4", 8/1994; 2.0 Videocassettes; Video; VHS; Dub; 60 min (Carton 17, Videotapes 6, 7)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps" Reels #2 & 3, 8/1994; 2.0 Videocassettes; Video; VHS; Dub; 30 min (Carton 17, Videotapes 8, 9)
    - Tape #10 "Tio Oscar"/Guaymas Transfer from Hi¯8, 5/1993; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min (Carton 17, Videotapes 10)
    - Devil Never Sleeps X.1 Reels #2 & #4 Mag Out, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 18, Reels 1, 2)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Dials 1¯4 Reel #3 Mag Out, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 18, Reels 3¯6)
    - Devil Never Sleeps ADR 1 & 2 Reel #3 Mag Out, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 18, Reels 7, 8)
    - Devil Never Sleeps FX¯1 Reel #3 Mag Out, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 18, Reels 9, 10)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Dials 1¯4 Reel #4 Mag Out, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 19, Reels 1¯4)
    - Devil Never Sleeps FX¯1, 2 Reel #4 Mag Out, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 19, Reels 5, 6)
    - Devil Never Sleeps ADR 1, 2 Reel #4 Mag Out, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 19, Reels 7, 8)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Sync Roll #17, 18, 20, 22, 23, nd; 5.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 20, Reels 1,3,5,7,9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Sync Roll #17, 18, 20, 22, 23, 5.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 20, Reels 2,4,6,8,10)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Sync Roll #24¯26, 34, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 21, Reels 1,3,5,7)
    - Tio Oscar Track Sync Roll #24¯26, 34, nd; 4.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 21, Reels 2,4,6,8)
    - Tio Oscar, SR 21¯40, 8/1993; 20.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 7"; (Carton 22, Reels 1¯20)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Music Reels 1¯4, nd; 4.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 7"; (Carton 22, Reels 21¯24)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps: Spanish Stereo Master for 16mm Optical R1¯4, nd; 4.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 10.5" (Carton 23, Reels 1¯4)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps: Split Mix Master Reels 1¯4, 1.0 Items; Audio; 2" open reel tape; Master; 10.5" (Carton 23, Reels 5)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Reels 1¯4, 1/1995; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic (Carton 24, Videotapes 1¯4)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Logos Etc., 2/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic; Logos (Carton 24, Videotape 5)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Subtitled Version R1¯4, 1/1995; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic; ~20 min each (Carton 24, Videotapes 6¯9)
    - Oscar R. 1¯4 ITVS Cut, 1/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic (Carton 24, Videotape 10)
    - Tio Oscar ¯ SR 1¯20, 8/1993; 20.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 7" (Carton 25, Reels 1¯20)
    - Tio Oscar ¯ SR 41¯58, B1¯B5, 7/1993 & 1/1994; 20.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 7" (Carton 26, Reels 1¯18)
    - Lourdes Portillo 477¯0820, 1.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 7" (Carton 26, Reel 19)
    - Tio Oscar ADR Rolls #1¯3, 7/1994; 3.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" open reel tape; Master; 10.5" (Carton 26, Reels 20¯22)
    - D.N.S. ADR, 7/1994; 1.0 Items; Audio; 2" open reel tape; Master; 10.5" (Carton 27, Reel 1)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps split Mixes Reel #1¯4, 2/1995; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video; DCS Digital Videocassette; Two 30 min and Two 60 min tapes (Carton 27, Videotapes 2¯5)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Sync Rolls #1¯6, nd; 6.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 28, Reels 1,3,5,7,9,11)
    - Tio Oscar Track Sync Rolls #1¯6, nd; 6.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 28, Reels 2,4,6,8,10,12)
    - ITVS Producer's Spot Reel, 5/1994; 1.0 Items; Video; 1" open reel video; Logos, etc. (Carton 29, Videotape 1)
    - Nat'l Lation Community Center Animated Logos Plus Elements, 11/1992; 1.0 Items; Video; 1" open reel video; Logos, etc. (Carton 29, Videotape 2)
    - CPB Narration Tags, 3/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Audio Master; 20 min (Carton 29, Videotape 3)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Subtitled version R1¯4, 1/1995; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Sub Master; ~20 min each tape (Carton 29, Videotape 4¯7)
    - Tio Oscar Reel 1¯4 Film Transfer, 12/1994; 4.0 Videocassettes; Video; 3/4" Umatic; Window Dub (Carton 29, Videotape 8¯11)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Assembly Reel #1¯3, 17, 19, nd; 5.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 30, Reels 1,3,5,7,9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Assembly Reel #1¯3, 17, 19, nd; 5.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 30, Reels 2,4,6,8,10)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Sync Rolls #7¯11, nd; 5.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 31, Reels 1,3,5,7,9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Sync Rolls #7¯11, nd; 5.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 31, Reels 2,4,6,8,10)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Sync Rolls #12, #14¯16, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 32, Reels 1,3,5,7)
    - Tio Oscar Track Sync Rolls #12, #14¯16, nd; 4.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 32, Reels 2,4,6,8)
    - Tio Oscar Pix Assembly Roll #20, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; 1000ft. (Carton 32, Reel 9)
    - Tio Oscar Track Assembly Roll #20, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 32, Reel 10)
    - Tio Oscar Sync Pix Rolls #21, 27, 29, 30¯33, nd; 8.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 33, Reels 1,3,5,7,9,11,13)
    - Tio Oscar Sync Track Rolls #21, 27, 29, 30¯33, nd; 7.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 33, Reels 2,4,6,8,10,12,14)
    - Tio Oscar Wild Track Rolls 17, 19¯22, B1¯B6, nd; 11.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 34, Reels 1¯11)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Reel #1 Dialogue 1¯4, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 35, Reels 1¯4)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Reel 1 FX 1¯4, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 35, Reels 5¯8)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Reel 1 X1, X2, nd; 2.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 35, Reels 9, 10)
    - Devil Never Sleeps ADR 1 & 2 Reels # 1 & 2, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 36, Reels 1¯4)
    - Devil Never Sleeps Reel #2 FX 1¯4, nd; 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 36, Reels 5¯8)
    - Tio Oscar Sync Pix Roll # 19, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (Carton 36, Reels 9)
    - Tio Oscar Sync Track Roll #19, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio; 16mm Full Coat Mag Stock; Master (Carton 36, Reels 10)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Optical Tracks ¯ Reels 2 & 4 (and 2 clips), 4.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (2 clip reels with ~1ft. of film on the cores) (Carton 37, Reels 1¯4)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Optical Tracks ¯ Reels 1 & 3 (and 1 clip), 3.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~1000ft. (1 clip reel with ~1ft. of film on the cores) (Carton 37, Reels 5¯7)
    - Tio Oscar Chihuahua Audio Only Tapes 1¯6, 7/1993; 6.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotape 1¯6)
    - Dania and Abuelitos; Snake Story, 3/1993; 2.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 60 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 7, 8)
    - Abuelita and Chencho, 3/1993; 3.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 9¯11)
    - Tio Oscar Interview with Catalina, 4/1993; 3.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 12¯14)
    - Tio Oscar Guaymas Is. I¯III, Catch 22 Set, nd; 3.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (2), 20 min (1) (Carton 38, Videotapes 15¯17)
    - Tio Oscar Shoot, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 120 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 18)
    - Tio Oscar, Tijuana, 6/27/1993; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 19)
    - E. Portillo ¯ Scout, 3/1993; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Hi¯8; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotapes 20)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps" Stereo Music, 11/1997; 2.0 Computer Media; Audio; DAT; Master; 120 min (1), 60 min (1) (Carton 38, Audiocassettes 21, 22)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps Music DAT, 8/199?; 1.0 Computer Media; Audio; DAT; Master; 30 min (Carton 38, Audiocassettes 23)
    - Devil Never Sleeps FX, nd; 1.0 Computer Media; Audio; DAT; Master; 120 min (Carton 38, Audiocassettes 24)
    - Tio Oscar: Lulu pickup Voice Over & Camera Clicks, 1/1994; 1.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Audiocassette; Master (Carton 38, Audiocassettes 25)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Audiocassette; Master; 90 min (Carton 38, Audiocassettes 26)
    - Tio Oscar Trailer with Subtitles, 1/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Edited Master; 13 min (Carton 38, Videotape 27)
    - Tio Oscar Telenovela selects, 8/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Edited Master; 20 min (Carton 38, Videotape 28)
    - Tio Oscar Ophelia Voice Over, 5/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video; Betacam SP; Dub; 30 min (Carton 38, Videotape 29)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps" English version pickups, 8/1994; 1.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Open Reel; Master; 7" (Carton 38, Reel 30)
    - Tio Oscar Video Shoot SR 1001, 1002, 4/1994; 2.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Open Reel; Master; 7" (Carton 38, Reel 31, 32)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Narration SR #1¯3, 6/1994; 3.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Open Reel; Master; 7" (Carton 38, Reel 33¯35)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps Narration SR 1¯3, 7/1994; 3.0 Items; Audio; 1/4" Open Reel; Master; 7" (Carton 38, Reel 36¯38)
    - The Devil Never Sleeps (60 min version), nd; 1.0 Items; Video; VHS; Dub; 60 min (Carton 38, Item 39)
    - "The Devil Never Sleeps" ¯ Final Mix Combine for 16mm Optical, 8/1994; 4.0 Items; Audio; 35mm Full Coat Mag Track; Master; 2500 ft. (Boxes 119¯122)
    - "Tio Oscar", nd; 5.0 Items; Audio; 35mm Full Coat Mag Track; Master; 2100 ft. (Boxes 123¯127)
  - Sor Juana: The Tenth Muse, circa 1995
    - Videotapes: "Sor Juana" ¯ Mexican Tv, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 1)
    - Videotapes: "Sor Juana Hoy" ¯ X. Cuevas, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 30 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 2)
    - Videotapes: "Sor Juana" ¯ Dr. Elias Trabulse, 1/1994; 1.0 Items; Video: VHS; Dub; 120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 3)
    - Cassette Tapes: Sor Juana Meeting #1¯#3, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" Cassette Tape; Original; ~100 min. (Carton 79, Audiocassettes 4¯6)
    - Videotapes: Dr. Elias Trabulse, nd; 1.0 Items; Video: Video8; Original; 120 min. (Carton 79, Videotape 7)
  - Sometimes My Feet Go Numb, 1997
    - Positive: Life With HIV Episode #103: "Care", nd; Video; Betacam SP; Broascast Master; ~60 min (Carton 43, Videotape 19)
    - Positive: Life With HIV Episode #103, #104: "Care" and "Fighting For Our Lives", Video; VHS; Dub; ~120 min (Carton 43, Videotape 20)
    - Positive: Life With HIV Episodes #101, #102: "Community" and " Identity", Video; VHS; Dub; ~120 min (Carton 43, Videotape 21)
    - Sometimes My Feet Go Numb, 6/1996; Video; Betacam SP; Protection Copy; 2:23 (Carton 43, Videotape 22)
  - Frontline: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas, circa 1998
    - Ernesto Zedillo ¯ Toma de Posesion, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 1)
    - Presentacion Plan Nacional de Desarrollo 1995¯2000, Presidente Ernesto Zedillo, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 2)
    - Mexican News: 2/95, 2/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 3)
    - Mexican News, 3/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 4)
    - Manuel Camacho Solis: Eventos Realizados Entre 1988 y 1995, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 6)
    - Testimonia les Reyes Pendgos: Centro de Derecos Humanos Yankin, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 7)
    - Interview with Denise Dresser, 7/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 10)
    - Frontline Scout #2, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 11)
    - Frontline Scout #3, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 12)
    - Mexico: End of An Era, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 13)
    - Cerpropie (Zedillo), nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 14)
    - Salinas News, 12/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 15)
    - Mexican News: Angels, 8/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 16)
    - Go Back To Mexico, 7/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 17)
    - Macneil/Lehrer News: Salinas, 8/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: Betacam; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 18)
    - From Boom to Bust, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~60 min (Carton 58, Videotape 19)
    - Conferencia De Prensa: Dr. Ernesto Zedillo Ponce De Leon A Los Medios De Comunicacion #1, 7/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 20)
    - Conferencia De Prensa: Dr. Ernesto Zedillo Ponce De Leon A Los Medios De Comunicacion #2, 7/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 21)
    - Conferencia De Prensa Dr. Ernesto Zedillo Ponce De Leon A Los Medios De Comunicacion #1, 6/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 22)
    - Conferencia De Prensa Dr. Ernesto Zedillo Ponce De Leon A Los Medios De Comunicacion #2, 6/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 23)
    - Conferencia De Prensa Dr. Ernesto Zedillo Ponce De Leon A Los Medios De Comunicacion #3, 6/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: BetacamSP; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 24)
    - Carcel a Salinas, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 42 min (Carton 58, Videotape 25)
    - Salinas Interview for "Getting Out Of Business", 1986; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 26)
    - Salinas Interview for "American Interest" Part I, 1990; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 27)
    - Salinas Interview for "American Interest" Part II, 1990; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~30 min (Carton 58, Videotape 28)
    - Mexico: Shortened Assembly, 1/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 88min (Carton 58, Videotape 29)
    - Rise & Fall, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 88min (Carton 58, Videotape 30)
    - Colosio's Murder, 3/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; ~120 min (Carton 58, Videotape 31)
    - Audio Tapes: Interview with Carlos Hank by Tom Gjelten, Mexico, D.F., 4/1995; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 10.5 in. reel (Carton 59, Reel 1)
    - Video Tapes: Window Dubs from Field Tapes 7 & 8, Log #9, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 4)
    - Video Tapes: Window Dubs from Field Tapes 8 & 9, Log #10, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 5)
    - Video Tapes: Multivision Entrevista A Marcela, 3/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~60 min (Carton 59, Videotape 6)
    - Video Tapes: Frontline: Tio Oscar ¯ Reels 1¯4, 1/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 8)
    - Video Tapes: Frontline: Tio Oscar ¯ Reels 5¯7, 1/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 9)
    - Video Tapes: Ten Years of Mexican History Reel #6, 11/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Dub; ~60 min (Carton 59, Videotape 10)
    - Video Tapes: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Photo Stills 2, 2/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~30 min (Carton 59, Videotape 11)
    - Video Tapes: Mexico: Ernesto Zedillo, 11/1995; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 12)
    - Video Tapes: Frontline Footage, 1/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; ~30 min (Carton 59, Videotape 13)
    - Audio Tapes: Frontline ¯ Mexico ¯ Sr 02, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 59, Reel 15)
    - Audio Tapes: Frontline ¯ Mexico ¯ Sr 03, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 59, Reel 16)
    - Audio Tapes: Frontline ¯ Mexico ¯ Sr 04, nd; 1.0 Items; Audio: 1/4" open reel; Master; 5 in. reel (Carton 59, Reel 17)
    - Video Tapes: Frontline Footage ¯ Sub Master, 1/1996; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: Betacam SP; Sub Master; ~20 min (Carton 59, Videotape 18)
    - Video Tapes: Frontline Footage ¯ Sub Master ¯ Edited Version Of Tunnel, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Sub Master; ~30 min (Carton 59, Videotape 19)
    - Video Tapes: Canal 40: Ciudades Violentas Caso Piloto, nd; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Dub; ~160 min (Carton 59, Videotape 20)
    - Film: Frontline Rolls 1 ¯ 5 (34064)¯ Beige Box, nd; 1.0 Items; Film: 16mm; Master; ~600 ft. (Carton 59, Reel 21)
    - Video Tapes: Mas Alla Del Puente: Mexican Presidential Debate, 5/1994; 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Dub; ~120 min (Carton 59, Videotape 22)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #01 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 1)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #02 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 2)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #03 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 3)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #04 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 4)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #05 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Viewing Copy; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 5)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #06 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 6)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #07 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 7)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #08 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 8)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #09 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 9)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #10 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 10)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #11 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 11)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #12 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 12)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #13 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 13)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #14 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 14)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #15 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 15)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #16 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 16)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #17 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 17)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #18 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 18)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #19 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 19)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #20 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 20)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #21 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 21)
    - Original Footage Tapes Mexico: The Rise and Fall of Carlos Salinas Tapes #22 English & Spanish, 1.0 Videocassettes; Video: VHS; Window Dub; 30 min (Carton 60, Videotape 22)